John N. Rowe III papers, Inclusive: 1510-1989, undated, Bulk: 1830-1880
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Early Texas Documents, 1801-1989, undated; 2
  - Financial, 1802-1925, undated; 3
    - Financial: County of Dallas: General Fund Warrant, Series 1940, 1947, 1948, 1940-1948 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 31)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Hospital Bonds, 1921, 1946 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 32)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Juvenile Building Bond, Series 1948 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 33)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Levee Improvement District No. 2, 1918 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 34)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Levee Improvement Refunding Bond, Districts 6 & 14, 1928-1960 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 35)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Road and Bridge Bond, Series 3, 5, 1917, 1935-1951 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 36)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Road and Bridge Refunding Bond, Series 1934-B, 1947, 1948, 1934-1948 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 37)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Road and Bridge Refunding Bond, Series 1934, 1945, 1946, 1948-A, 1951, 1934-1951 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 38)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Road and Bridge Warrant, Series 1938 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 39)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Road Bond, District No. 1, Series 1928, 1951, 1958, 2, 5, 6, 1919, 1921, 1928-1930, 1958 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 40)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Road Bonds, Series 1942, 1945, 1947, 1945-A, 1950-1951, 1942-1951 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 41)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bonds, 1913 March 10 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 42)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bond: Common School Districts #3-#50, 1916 February (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 43)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bond: Common School District #52-#100, 1914-1919 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 44)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bond: Cockrell Hill Independent School District, 1916 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 45)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bond: Consolidated Common School District #24, 1916 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 46)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bond: Shady Grove Common School District #3, 1950 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 47)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bond: Trinity Heights Independent School District, 1916 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 48)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Viaduct and Bridge Bond, Series #3 & #4, 1914 (Box 47 OVZ, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Estate of J. Y. Crisswell, undated (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Financial: The Boston & Texas Central Railway Company—Bond, 1873 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Assorted Blank Promissory Notes for the Republic and State of Texas (One filled out for Thomas Dypert, 1841), 1841, 1846 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Bridge Repair Bond, 1908 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Financial: State of Texas—Bond, $100.00, 1874 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Financial: County of Dallas: Schoolhouse Bond: Common School District #38, #57, #76 & #82, 1906-1912 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Corsicana Gas Light Company, 1886 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Other, 1815-1921, undated; 4
    Other is the fourth subseries and contains materials in languages other than English and Spanish, such as German, French, and Latin. It also holds early flyers, sheet music, invitations, tickets, circulars, publications, and a section of letters and documents from the Arthur Stiles family. The Stiles family materials are three document boxes of correspondence and business records from Arthur's surveying business.
    - Other: 1848 (Latin text) (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Other: Arnold, Johann, N. Runge (German text), 1856 October 5 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Other: Barbet, Mme. Geo. W: Funeral Notice, New Orleans (French text), 1899 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Other: Barbyat, J. E. (French text), 1842 April 9 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Other: Billy the Kid, Pat Garrett -Newspaper Clipping, unidentified, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Other: Brann’s Iconoclast, 1897 February (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Other: “Carpenters & Joiners Scale of Prices” circular, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Other: Cinco Pesos-El Bancode Tamaulipas, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Other: Crescent College “Ticket-High School Girls Basketball”, 1921 April 7 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Other: Diaz, Perfecto, Map of Brazos County, undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Other: Ellison, William, J. C. Crawford, Claiborne Kyle, H. Niel, Witless Jones “Election Returns for State Senate”, 1853 August 12 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Other: Envelopes, 1888-1899 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Other: Envelopes for the Texas Centennial, 1836 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Other: Envelope from Gillespie County, Texas-Centennial to Fredricksburg, Texas, 1936 May 8 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Other: Eugene Digges, Bookseller: Texas: The Country and Its Men, by L. E. Daniel-flyer, undated (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Other: Fannin, James W. (Havana, Cuba), 1832 May 30 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Other: “Flagsong of Texas” Sheet, 1903 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Other: Galveston Tribune, 1815 August 19 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Other: Gauwain, Henry Bock (German Text), 1847 August 30 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Other: General Order No. 8, United Sons of Confederate Veterans, Waco, Texas, 1903 May 4 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Other: “Greenback Ticket” -Election List, undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Other: W. JJ. (Jones, William J.) “Sea Island Cotton in Cultivation” (Galveston), 1858 January (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Other: King, S. M. -flyer: “Save Your Homes, Protect Your Families”, undated (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Other: Map- Battle of Palo Alto, 1846 May (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Other: Marshall, F. P. -Answer to J. A. Spear’s circular of July 22nd, undated (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Other: McClelland, JB—Texas Land Company, 1860 June 11 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Other: Program: Preparatory School Prize Declamation, 1886 June 3 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Other: Sargant, George S., Schooner [Illegible], 1862 January 18 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Other: Texas “Black Gold Certificate” -Promotional item, undated (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Other: Texas Mutual Life Insurance Company Advertisement, undated (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Other: Tintype Photograph, Unknown Couple, Circa 1859 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Other: Young Men’s Christian Association of San Antonio, 1891 March 1 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: Arthur’s Introduction, 1940 September (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1858, 1860-1863 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1864 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1866 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1867 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1868 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1869 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1870 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1872 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1874 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1875 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (1 of 2), 1876 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (2 of 2), 1876 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (1 of 2), 1877 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (2 of 2), 1877 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1878 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (1 of 2), 1879 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (2 of 2), 1879 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (1 of 3), 1880 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (2 of 3), 1880 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (3 of 3), 1880 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1881 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1883 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1884 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1885-1886 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1887, 1889 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1891 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1892 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (1 of 2), 1895-1896 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (2 of 2), 1895-1896 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1897 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1898 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1899 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1900 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1901 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1902 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence:, 1903 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (1 of 2), 1904 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Other: Stiles Family: Correspondence: (2 of 2), 1904 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1905 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1906 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1914 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1916 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1917 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1920 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence:, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence: Arthur Stiles Letters to Mother, 1894, 1904 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence: Personal Correspondence, 1891-1898, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence: Letters to Arthur Stiles (1 of 2), 1893-1905 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence: Letters to Arthur Stiles (2 of 2), 1893-1905 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Other: Styles Family: Correspondence: Arthur Stiles Professional Correspondence, 1894-1906, 1931-1933, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Other: Styles Family: Account Book: William Stiles, 1877 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Other: Styles Family: Baltimore Stockbridge: Letters and Financial Documents (1 of 5), 1898-1903 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Other: Styles Family: Baltimore Stockbridge: Letters and Financial Documents (2 of 5), 1898-1903 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Other: Styles Family: Baltimore Stockbridge: Letters and Financial Documents (3 of 5), 1898-1903 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Other: Styles Family: Baltimore Stockbridge: Letters and Financial Documents (4 of 5), 1898-1903 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Other: Styles Family: Baltimore Stockbridge: Letters and Financial Documents (5 of 5), 1898-1903 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Other: Styles Family: Diploma: American Society of Civil Engineers, 1942 March 13 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Other: Styles Family: Envelopes, 1894 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Other: Styles Family: H.G. Avers: Precise Leveling in Texas, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Other: Styles Family: Report of the State Reclamation Engineer, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Other: Styles Family: Report of Surveys, 1902, 1921-1922, 1932-1934 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Other: Styles Family: Triangulation Notes: Arthur Stiles, 1909-1912, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Other: Styles Family: US Geological Survey Traverse Book, undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Other: French Documents, 1783-1784 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 1)
- Early United States Documents, 1767, 1834-1976, undated; 3
  The Early United States Documents series contains early documents relating to the United States apart from Texas. Confederate State currency, United States currency, bank notes and script from non-Texas states, treasury warrants, United States treaties with individual Indian tribes, and correspondence call be found in this section of the papers.
  - “Account of the Terrible and Fatal Riot at the New York Astor Place Opera HouseEL.”, 1849 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Acevez, Bernardino, William H. McBloom, 1883 February 5 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Augusta Savings Bank-Certificate of Deposit, 1861 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Berry, James M.-Louisiana, 1846 August 25 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Bicentennial, 1976 July 4 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Bishop’s Central Store House, Salt Lake City, Utah, merchandise certificate, 1898 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Brunstetter, Peter-Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, 1876, 1878 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Buisson, Onezime vs. M. Dupas, 1848 April 19 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Carson, J.J., 1894 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - City of New Orleans Tax Document, 1860 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Confederate States Currency-Georgia, $.10 cents, 1863 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Confederate States Currency-Alabama, $.10 cents, 1863 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Confederate States Currency-Virginia, $.50 cents, 1864 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Confederate States of America-Confederate States Depository (Blank), 1860s (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Confederate States of America, $20.00 note, 1864 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Confederate States of America-certificate, $100.00, 1864 July 25 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Confederate States of America, $100.00 notes, 1862 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Confederate States of America, $2.00 notes, 1862-1863 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Confederate States of America, $1.00 notes, 1862 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Confederate States of America, $10.00 notes, 1861-1863 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Confederate States of America-certificate, $1,000.00, 1865 March 9 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Connally, Tom-United States Senate, 1934 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Currency: The Bank of the Old Dominion, Pearisburg, Virginia-1 ¼ (One Dollar and Twenty-Five Cents), 1862 May 1 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Currency: Canal Bank, New Orleans, Louisiana, $10.00, $20.00, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Currency: Citizens Bank of Louisiana, $100.00, $5.00, 1864, undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Currency: Maryland, $2.00, 1767 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Currency: The State of Mississippi, $10.00, 1862 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Currency: The Mississippi & Alabama Rail Road Company, $10.00, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Currency: Pennsylvania, Lacawanna Valley Coal Company, $.50 cents, 1860s (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Currency: The United States Insurance Company of Baltimore, $2,500.00, 1834 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Currency: United States of America, $.25 cent note, undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Currency: United States of America, $.50 cent note, undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Currency: United States of America, $5.00 note, 1863 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Currency: United States of America, National Bank of Galveston, $5.00 note, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Currency: Virginia Treasury Note, $1.00, 1862 July 21 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Drew, Newitt, Richard H. Thompson, Sarah Drew, 1846 August 25 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Eberle, Jacob, Pennsylvania-treasury warrant, 1865 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Faulk, Governor A.J.-Third Annual Message to Legislative Assembly of the Territory of Dakota, 1869 December (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Forstall, C., Louisiana-treasury warrant, 1871 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Giddings, D.C., 1872 June 4 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Goebelman & Company, Cincinnati, Ohio-receipt (Richard Wolley & Sons), 1870s (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Henderson & Company, American Express Company, The American Tailors, 1893-1895 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Henneman, J.S., 1893 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Johnson, Luke, Levi Alred, Mississippi, 1846 April 15 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Kansas City Clearing House, 1917 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Larkman, James M., C.R. Chapman, California, 1874 September (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Macmurdo, Gray & Company, Louisiana, 1851 March 18 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - McConoughey, J.M., W.R. Miller, Arkansas-bond, 1861 August 17 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - McNeill, John P., Henry Harrison, Mississippi, Louisiana, undated (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Montgomery, John, John Ralston, Alabama, 1847 November 2 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Negotiations With Mexico, 51st Congress, 1st Session, 1890 May 9 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Poem: “He Was A Confederate Soldier”-unidentified, undated (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Rector, Elbridge Geary, Laura A. Rector, California, 1865-1909 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Resolution: General Assembly of Connecticut, Adverse to the Annexation of Texas, 1844 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Richard, G.W.-U.S. Mint, Memorandum of Gold Bullion, 1899 October 6 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Robertson, James W.-California, 1874 June 3 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Rogers, R.W.-Confederate note, 1862 July 7 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Sheppard, Morris-United States Senate, 1934 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Smith, W.E., Stillwell H. Russell, 1878 September 6 (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Stiles, William C., Kentucky, 1845 December 20 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Thompson, Colonel G.S.-“Santa Anna”, 1867 July 29 (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Train, Henry, Louisiana-treasury warrant, 1871 (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Treasury Warrant, Louisiana, 1875 (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Treaty Between The United States of America and the Confederated Tribes of Sacs and Foxes of the Mississippi, 1859-1860 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Treaty Between The United States of America and the Nez Perce Tribe of Indians, 1863,1867 (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Treaty Between The United States of America and the Pottawatomie Tribe of Indians, 1861 November 15 (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Treaty Between The United States of America and the Sans Arcs Band of Dakota or Sioux Indians, 1865-1866 (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Twohig, John, New York, Consolidated Bank, 1882 May 22 (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - United States Distillery Warehouse Stamp, 1800s (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - United States Government Depository, 1860s (blank check) (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - United States Internal Revenue Stamp for Special Tax-Dealer in Manufactured Tobacco, 1875, 1876, 1884 (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - United States Internal Revenue Stamp for Special Tax-Retail Liquor Dealer, 1871, 1880, undated (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - United States Senate, Amendment to H.R. 692, 1849 February (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - United States Senate, Report by Mr. Rusk, 1848 April 7 (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - United States Sentinel, 1855 January (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Wandell, William A., 1853 February 21 (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - Ward, Shadrac, North Carolina, 1864 September 29 (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Wooster, Clark, 1841 October 25 (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - City of New Orleans, Louisiana, $1,000 certificate, 1862 March 20 (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Capper’s Farmer, Topeka, Kansas, undated (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Blank Check: First National Bank, Dodge City, Kansas, 1800s (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Confederate Loan Documents-Bonds, 1863 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Confederate States of America—Bonds $1,000.00, 1863, 1865 (Box 49 OVZ, Folder 4)